http://www.e-yearbook.com/sp/terms?privacy=1

Digital Data Online, Inc. E-Yearbook Website Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is effective as of October 15, 2006 and may be
updated from time to time.  If you have not reviewed it since
that date, please do so as the prior version is no longer in effect.
You will not receive any other notice of changes to this statement.
Overview Legal
Disclosure
We may disclose your personally identifiable information if required to
do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary
to conform to applicable law, comply with a judicial proceeding, court
order or legal process served, protect and defend the rights or
property of DDO or E-Yearbook, or investigate, prevent or take action
regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving
potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or violations
of our Terms of Service.
The personal, private information that is provided to us by individual
members is not provided to unrelated third parties except in rare cases
described below or involving possible violations of our Terms and
Conditions or as may be required by law.  We do collect some
data, always with your knowledge, that is used to fulfill orders and
otherwise enhance content to better meet the needs of our users. We
collect your information at various points when you use the Website.
This is described in more detail below.
When You Register
During the process of registering on the Website, you may be required
to provide certain personal contact information such as your name,
mailing address, e-mail address, phone number, birth date,
password, and an affiliation.  To facilitate payment and
fulfillment in connection with subscribing as a member we will request
personal credit card information. Credit card information is collected
so that we can process subscription fees. We use a credit card
processing company to process fees. This company does not retain,
share, store or use personally identifiable information for any
secondary purposes. We reserve the right to provide aggregated user
data to third parties for marketing and promotion purposes but not in a
form that discloses your personally identifiable information.
We do not rent, sell or distribute personal information to advertisers.
When You Browse the
Site
When you browse through the Website, whether as a registered user or
not, our systems track and retain certain information about the pages
you have viewed.
Log
Files
Like most standard website servers, we use and maintain the information
that we obtain from your browser on our server logs. This information
can include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet
service provider ("ISP"), and other data. We may use this information
to analyze trends, administer the Website, track user movement in the
aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.
We may associate this information with your personal information to
resolve technical issues and support security for our users.
Cookies
Contrary to popular misconception, cookies do not extract private or
personal information from your computer’s memory, but rather,
record only information you volunteer upon registering or visiting the
Website. Cookies are tiny files placed onto the hard drive of your
computer when you register at our Website that enable our server to
recognize or "remember" who you are each time you return. Our primary
use of cookies is to improve your experience on the Website. For
example, storing a cookie on your computer allows you to login without
typing the registered e-mail address or registration number and
password.
The "Tell-A-Friend"
Feature
If you elect to use our referral service to tell a friend about our
Website, you will be asked to provide your friend's name and e-mail
address. We will then automatically send the friend a one-time e-mail
inviting them to visit the Website. We ask for this information for the
sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail and tracking the success
of our referral program.
Legal Disclosure
We may disclose your personally identifiable information if required to
do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary
to conform to applicable law, comply with a judicial proceeding, court
order or legal process served, protect and defend the rights or
property of DDO or E-Yearbook, or investigate, prevent or take action
regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving
potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or violations
of our Terms of Service.
No Underage Users
Please note that NO PART OF THE SITE IS INTENDED FOR USE BY THOSE UNDER
18 AND DDO DOES NOT KNOWINGLY COLLECT OR MAINTAIN INFORMATION ON THE
SITE FROM THOSE UNDER 18.
Communications From
Us
If you have registered as a subscriber, you will receive our standard
communications (e.g., confirmation of subscription, notice of renewal
and similar communications).  In addition, you may be
automatically enrolled in one or more of our e-mail newsletter
programs.  You have the opportunity to opt-out if you do not
wish to receive such communications.
The Security Of
Your Information
We have instituted physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to
store and maintain your information in a secure environment. For
example, when highly confidential information, such as a credit card
number, is transmitted through our Website, it is encrypted by using
Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software. You may also be required to use a
password to access certain pages on the Website where certain types of
your information can be changed or deleted. It is therefore important
for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password, emails
which we may send you and to your computer. You take full
responsibility for maintaining the confidentiality of your password.
Furthermore, while we have implemented safeguards we are not in a
position to guarantee that your information will be secure under all
circumstances.
Copyright © 2005-2020
Digital Data Online, Inc.
Material on this website is protected by copyright laws of the United States and international treaties. All copyrights remain the property of the copyright owner. No images or material on this website may be copied or printed without express authorization. For further information about copyright laws visit the U.S. Copyright Office.
